{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331461872","data":{"timestamp":" 947331461872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331463834","data":{"timestamp":" 947331463834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331465394","data":{"timestamp":" 947331465394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331467446","data":{"timestamp":" 947331467446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331469014","data":{"timestamp":" 947331469014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331471246","data":{"timestamp":" 947331471246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331472819","data":{"timestamp":" 947331472819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331476967","data":{"timestamp":" 947331476967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331478545","data":{"timestamp":" 947331478545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331481272","data":{"timestamp":" 947331481272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331482844","data":{"timestamp":" 947331482844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331489409","data":{"timestamp":" 947331489409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" START_F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331494899","data":{"timestamp":" 947331494899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331496488","data":{"timestamp":" 947331496488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331499075","data":{"timestamp":" 947331499075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331500654","data":{"timestamp":" 947331500654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331513541","data":{"timestamp":" 947331513541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331515129","data":{"timestamp":" 947331515128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331517589","data":{"timestamp":" 947331517589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331519155","data":{"timestamp":" 947331519155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331521484","data":{"timestamp":" 947331521484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331523046","data":{"timestamp":" 947331523045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331525465","data":{"timestamp":" 947331525465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331527023","data":{"timestamp":" 947331527023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331535615","data":{"timestamp":" 947331535615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331537202","data":{"timestamp":" 947331537202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331539684","data":{"timestamp":" 947331539683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331541263","data":{"timestamp":" 947331541262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331543462","data":{"timestamp":" 947331543461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331545035","data":{"timestamp":" 947331545035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331547123","data":{"timestamp":" 947331547123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331548688","data":{"timestamp":" 947331548688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331552790","data":{"timestamp":" 947331552790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331554364","data":{"timestamp":" 947331554364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331557759","data":{"timestamp":" 947331557759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331559326","data":{"timestamp":" 947331559326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331561928","data":{"timestamp":" 947331561928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331563490","data":{"timestamp":" 947331563490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331566152","data":{"timestamp":" 947331566152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331567721","data":{"timestamp":" 947331567721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331569854","data":{"timestamp":" 947331569854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331571425","data":{"timestamp":" 947331571425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331574095","data":{"timestamp":" 947331574095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331575658","data":{"timestamp":" 947331575657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331577759","data":{"timestamp":" 947331577759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331579327","data":{"timestamp":" 947331579327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331581958","data":{"timestamp":" 947331581958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331583525","data":{"timestamp":" 947331583525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331586277","data":{"timestamp":" 947331586277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331588285","data":{"timestamp":" 947331588284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331588357","data":{"timestamp":" 947331588356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 159610dd-2044-490b-a3d2-982e6bb03e86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331623152","data":{"timestamp":" 947331623152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331624223","data":{"timestamp":" 947331624223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331628159","data":{"timestamp":" 947331628158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331629221","data":{"timestamp":" 947331629220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331632542","data":{"timestamp":" 947331632541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331633588","data":{"timestamp":" 947331633588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331636168","data":{"timestamp":" 947331636167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331637231","data":{"timestamp":" 947331637230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331640564","data":{"timestamp":" 947331640563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331641623","data":{"timestamp":" 947331641622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331645348","data":{"timestamp":" 947331645348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331646408","data":{"timestamp":" 947331646408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331652469","data":{"timestamp":" 947331652469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331653561","data":{"timestamp":" 947331653560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331659852","data":{"timestamp":" 947331659851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331660904","data":{"timestamp":" 947331660903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331664510","data":{"timestamp":" 947331664510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331665573","data":{"timestamp":" 947331665573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331670209","data":{"timestamp":" 947331670208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331671272","data":{"timestamp":" 947331671271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331674320","data":{"timestamp":" 947331674319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331675377","data":{"timestamp":" 947331675375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331681098","data":{"timestamp":" 947331681098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" START_L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331683752","data":{"timestamp":" 947331683752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331684849","data":{"timestamp":" 947331684849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331687754","data":{"timestamp":" 947331687753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331688807","data":{"timestamp":" 947331688807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331692403","data":{"timestamp":" 947331692403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331693473","data":{"timestamp":" 947331693472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331697069","data":{"timestamp":" 947331697068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331698140","data":{"timestamp":" 947331698139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331701807","data":{"timestamp":" 947331701806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331702859","data":{"timestamp":" 947331702858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331706609","data":{"timestamp":" 947331706609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331707673","data":{"timestamp":" 947331707672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331711801","data":{"timestamp":" 947331711800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331712875","data":{"timestamp":" 947331712874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331716510","data":{"timestamp":" 947331716510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331717576","data":{"timestamp":" 947331717575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331720432","data":{"timestamp":" 947331720432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331721492","data":{"timestamp":" 947331721492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331724774","data":{"timestamp":" 947331724773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331725826","data":{"timestamp":" 947331725825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331729780","data":{"timestamp":" 947331729779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331730856","data":{"timestamp":" 947331730855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331734375","data":{"timestamp":" 947331734374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331735441","data":{"timestamp":" 947331735441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331739116","data":{"timestamp":" 947331739116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331740172","data":{"timestamp":" 947331740172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331743582","data":{"timestamp":" 947331743580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331743711","data":{"timestamp":" 947331743711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 81327468-9ca7-49b6-8938-2fa157611fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331857051","data":{"timestamp":" 947331857051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331871225","data":{"timestamp":" 947331871225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331875104","data":{"timestamp":" 947331875104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331880104","data":{"timestamp":" 947331880104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331885421","data":{"timestamp":" 947331885421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331891642","data":{"timestamp":" 947331891642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331896550","data":{"timestamp":" 947331896550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331902320","data":{"timestamp":" 947331902320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331907194","data":{"timestamp":" 947331907194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331913612","data":{"timestamp":" 947331913612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331965583","data":{"timestamp":" 947331965583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331969829","data":{"timestamp":" 947331969828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947331978104","data":{"timestamp":" 947331978104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332037149","data":{"timestamp":" 947332037149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332044480","data":{"timestamp":" 947332044479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332048094","data":{"timestamp":" 947332048094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332055773","data":{"timestamp":" 947332055773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332060112","data":{"timestamp":" 947332060112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332064485","data":{"timestamp":" 947332064485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332080562","data":{"timestamp":" 947332080562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332086043","data":{"timestamp":" 947332086043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332089326","data":{"timestamp":" 947332089326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332092923","data":{"timestamp":" 947332092923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332096639","data":{"timestamp":" 947332096639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332102422","data":{"timestamp":" 947332102421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 7525238c-474e-4c8e-83e6-32f32eb6c2ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332147518","data":{"timestamp":" 947332147518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332147891","data":{"timestamp":" 947332147891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332148373","data":{"timestamp":" 947332148373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332148716","data":{"timestamp":" 947332148716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332149130","data":{"timestamp":" 947332149130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332149614","data":{"timestamp":" 947332149613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332149847","data":{"timestamp":" 947332149847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332153067","data":{"timestamp":" 947332153066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332153109","data":{"timestamp":" 947332153109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332153837","data":{"timestamp":" 947332153837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332154238","data":{"timestamp":" 947332154238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332154545","data":{"timestamp":" 947332154544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332154762","data":{"timestamp":" 947332154761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332154969","data":{"timestamp":" 947332154968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332155284","data":{"timestamp":" 947332155284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332155508","data":{"timestamp":" 947332155508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332158676","data":{"timestamp":" 947332158675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332159088","data":{"timestamp":" 947332159088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332161684","data":{"timestamp":" 947332161683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332161896","data":{"timestamp":" 947332161896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332162108","data":{"timestamp":" 947332162107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332165576","data":{"timestamp":" 947332165576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332169336","data":{"timestamp":" 947332169335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332170373","data":{"timestamp":" 947332170371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332173125","data":{"timestamp":" 947332173124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332173513","data":{"timestamp":" 947332173512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332174007","data":{"timestamp":" 947332174006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332174360","data":{"timestamp":" 947332174360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332174775","data":{"timestamp":" 947332174774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332175261","data":{"timestamp":" 947332175261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332175497","data":{"timestamp":" 947332175497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332178709","data":{"timestamp":" 947332178708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332178758","data":{"timestamp":" 947332178758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332179484","data":{"timestamp":" 947332179483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332179888","data":{"timestamp":" 947332179888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332180194","data":{"timestamp":" 947332180194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332180412","data":{"timestamp":" 947332180411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332180619","data":{"timestamp":" 947332180619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332180949","data":{"timestamp":" 947332180948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332181186","data":{"timestamp":" 947332181185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332183816","data":{"timestamp":" 947332183815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332183905","data":{"timestamp":" 947332183905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 73445337-11f6-48d7-a2bf-b21a7d36332d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332220582","data":{"timestamp":" 947332220582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332221220","data":{"timestamp":" 947332221220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332221476","data":{"timestamp":" 947332221476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332222042","data":{"timestamp":" 947332222041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332223201","data":{"timestamp":" 947332223200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332223969","data":{"timestamp":" 947332223969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332225391","data":{"timestamp":" 947332225390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332226293","data":{"timestamp":" 947332226292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332226936","data":{"timestamp":" 947332226935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332227879","data":{"timestamp":" 947332227878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332228529","data":{"timestamp":" 947332228528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332230961","data":{"timestamp":" 947332230960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332231217","data":{"timestamp":" 947332231216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332232157","data":{"timestamp":" 947332232156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332233046","data":{"timestamp":" 947332233045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332233898","data":{"timestamp":" 947332233897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPISHI"," userResponse":" MPISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332234807","data":{"timestamp":" 947332234806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332237533","data":{"timestamp":" 947332237532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332237968","data":{"timestamp":" 947332237968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332238677","data":{"timestamp":" 947332238676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332239737","data":{"timestamp":" 947332239736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332240676","data":{"timestamp":" 947332240675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332241507","data":{"timestamp":" 947332241507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONJA"," userResponse":" KUONJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332242462","data":{"timestamp":" 947332242462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332244090","data":{"timestamp":" 947332244089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332244301","data":{"timestamp":" 947332244300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332245162","data":{"timestamp":" 947332245162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332245874","data":{"timestamp":" 947332245874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332246187","data":{"timestamp":" 947332246187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332247069","data":{"timestamp":" 947332247069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332248143","data":{"timestamp":" 947332248142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332251212","data":{"timestamp":" 947332251211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332251828","data":{"timestamp":" 947332251828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332252939","data":{"timestamp":" 947332252939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332254086","data":{"timestamp":" 947332254085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPITA"," userResponse":" ALIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332254444","data":{"timestamp":" 947332254443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332255327","data":{"timestamp":" 947332255326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332256568","data":{"timestamp":" 947332256567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" RAFIKIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332257408","data":{"timestamp":" 947332257407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332260058","data":{"timestamp":" 947332260058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332260960","data":{"timestamp":" 947332260959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332261538","data":{"timestamp":" 947332261538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332261786","data":{"timestamp":" 947332261785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332262521","data":{"timestamp":" 947332262520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332263344","data":{"timestamp":" 947332263344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332266032","data":{"timestamp":" 947332266031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332267032","data":{"timestamp":" 947332267032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332267511","data":{"timestamp":" 947332267510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332267786","data":{"timestamp":" 947332267785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332268580","data":{"timestamp":" 947332268579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332269885","data":{"timestamp":" 947332269885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332270214","data":{"timestamp":" 947332270214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332271457","data":{"timestamp":" 947332271457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMUKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332272388","data":{"timestamp":" 947332272388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332273053","data":{"timestamp":" 947332273053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332273304","data":{"timestamp":" 947332273304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332274163","data":{"timestamp":" 947332274163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332274700","data":{"timestamp":" 947332274700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332275288","data":{"timestamp":" 947332275287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332275865","data":{"timestamp":" 947332275865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332278604","data":{"timestamp":" 947332278603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332279873","data":{"timestamp":" 947332279873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332280894","data":{"timestamp":" 947332280893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332282255","data":{"timestamp":" 947332282255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAZIJAIVA"," userResponse":" HAZIJAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332283307","data":{"timestamp":" 947332283306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332283832","data":{"timestamp":" 947332283832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332284976","data":{"timestamp":" 947332284976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBUNI"," userResponse":" KARIBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332286411","data":{"timestamp":" 947332286411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332287536","data":{"timestamp":" 947332287536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRI"," userResponse":" SUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332288069","data":{"timestamp":" 947332288069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332289014","data":{"timestamp":" 947332289014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332291595","data":{"timestamp":" 947332291595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332292559","data":{"timestamp":" 947332292559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332292853","data":{"timestamp":" 947332292852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332293607","data":{"timestamp":" 947332293607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332294980","data":{"timestamp":" 947332294980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332295651","data":{"timestamp":" 947332295650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332296084","data":{"timestamp":" 947332296083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332296937","data":{"timestamp":" 947332296936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332297978","data":{"timestamp":" 947332297978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332298458","data":{"timestamp":" 947332298458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332299410","data":{"timestamp":" 947332299410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJUKUMU"," userResponse":" MAJUKUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332299609","data":{"timestamp":" 947332299609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332300392","data":{"timestamp":" 947332300392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332303024","data":{"timestamp":" 947332303023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332304036","data":{"timestamp":" 947332304035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332305010","data":{"timestamp":" 947332305009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESUBIRI"," userResponse":" ANGESUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332306246","data":{"timestamp":" 947332306245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332306888","data":{"timestamp":" 947332306887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332308040","data":{"timestamp":" 947332308040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332308875","data":{"timestamp":" 947332308875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMPA"," userResponse":" ANGEMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332309628","data":{"timestamp":" 947332309627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332309797","data":{"timestamp":" 947332309796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332310562","data":{"timestamp":" 947332310561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332313694","data":{"timestamp":" 947332313694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332314989","data":{"timestamp":" 947332314984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWABIA"," userResponse":" AKAMWABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332315839","data":{"timestamp":" 947332315838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332318041","data":{"timestamp":" 947332318040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITASOKOTA"," userResponse":" NITASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332318921","data":{"timestamp":" 947332318921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332320147","data":{"timestamp":" 947332320146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFUNGE"," userResponse":" NIFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332320840","data":{"timestamp":" 947332320840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332321410","data":{"timestamp":" 947332321409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332322050","data":{"timestamp":" 947332322050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332323078","data":{"timestamp":" 947332323078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332323478","data":{"timestamp":" 947332323477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332324210","data":{"timestamp":" 947332324210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332324709","data":{"timestamp":" 947332324709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332325172","data":{"timestamp":" 947332325171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332325790","data":{"timestamp":" 947332325789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332328153","data":{"timestamp":" 947332328152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332329842","data":{"timestamp":" 947332329842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332331002","data":{"timestamp":" 947332331001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUTA"," userResponse":" VUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332331780","data":{"timestamp":" 947332331779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332332256","data":{"timestamp":" 947332332255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332333329","data":{"timestamp":" 947332333328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKIMBIA"," userResponse":" NITAKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332333898","data":{"timestamp":" 947332333897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJE"," userResponse":" NIJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332336560","data":{"timestamp":" 947332336559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332337479","data":{"timestamp":" 947332337478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332338199","data":{"timestamp":" 947332338198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332338389","data":{"timestamp":" 947332338388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332338912","data":{"timestamp":" 947332338911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332339646","data":{"timestamp":" 947332339645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332340215","data":{"timestamp":" 947332340214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332343161","data":{"timestamp":" 947332343160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332343788","data":{"timestamp":" 947332343787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332347060","data":{"timestamp":" 947332347059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332348461","data":{"timestamp":" 947332348460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332348748","data":{"timestamp":" 947332348748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332349624","data":{"timestamp":" 947332349624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332350899","data":{"timestamp":" 947332350898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332351784","data":{"timestamp":" 947332351783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332351879","data":{"timestamp":" 947332351879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332352229","data":{"timestamp":" 947332352229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332353302","data":{"timestamp":" 947332353301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332354254","data":{"timestamp":" 947332354254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332356253","data":{"timestamp":" 947332356252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332357104","data":{"timestamp":" 947332357103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332357210","data":{"timestamp":" 947332357210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332358208","data":{"timestamp":" 947332358207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332359681","data":{"timestamp":" 947332359680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332360727","data":{"timestamp":" 947332360727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332362295","data":{"timestamp":" 947332362294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPIKWA"," userResponse":" YANAPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332362866","data":{"timestamp":" 947332362864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332363621","data":{"timestamp":" 947332363620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332366614","data":{"timestamp":" 947332366614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332367856","data":{"timestamp":" 947332367856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWITA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332368655","data":{"timestamp":" 947332368655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332369768","data":{"timestamp":" 947332369767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332370376","data":{"timestamp":" 947332370376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332371359","data":{"timestamp":" 947332371359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332372221","data":{"timestamp":" 947332372221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332373344","data":{"timestamp":" 947332373343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332374446","data":{"timestamp":" 947332374446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATAIVA"," userResponse":" YATAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332377164","data":{"timestamp":" 947332377163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332378185","data":{"timestamp":" 947332378184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332379886","data":{"timestamp":" 947332379886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332380527","data":{"timestamp":" 947332380526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332380938","data":{"timestamp":" 947332380937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332381771","data":{"timestamp":" 947332381770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332384594","data":{"timestamp":" 947332384592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332385786","data":{"timestamp":" 947332385785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHAURI"," userResponse":" AKASHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332386401","data":{"timestamp":" 947332386400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332387255","data":{"timestamp":" 947332387254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332388548","data":{"timestamp":" 947332388547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATASOKOTA"," userResponse":" ATASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332389438","data":{"timestamp":" 947332389438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332390573","data":{"timestamp":" 947332390573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332391065","data":{"timestamp":" 947332391064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332391670","data":{"timestamp":" 947332391669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332392544","data":{"timestamp":" 947332392544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332393197","data":{"timestamp":" 947332393197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332393859","data":{"timestamp":" 947332393858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332394381","data":{"timestamp":" 947332394381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332395137","data":{"timestamp":" 947332395137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332395617","data":{"timestamp":" 947332395617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332396151","data":{"timestamp":" 947332396151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332397147","data":{"timestamp":" 947332397146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332397421","data":{"timestamp":" 947332397421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332398306","data":{"timestamp":" 947332398306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332400305","data":{"timestamp":" 947332400304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332401165","data":{"timestamp":" 947332401165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332402102","data":{"timestamp":" 947332402102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332402744","data":{"timestamp":" 947332402743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332402976","data":{"timestamp":" 947332402975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332403919","data":{"timestamp":" 947332403918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332405075","data":{"timestamp":" 947332405074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332405632","data":{"timestamp":" 947332405632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332406436","data":{"timestamp":" 947332406435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332407238","data":{"timestamp":" 947332407237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332407825","data":{"timestamp":" 947332407824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332408661","data":{"timestamp":" 947332408660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332409525","data":{"timestamp":" 947332409525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332410361","data":{"timestamp":" 947332410361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" WAKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332411056","data":{"timestamp":" 947332411056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332413016","data":{"timestamp":" 947332413016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332413561","data":{"timestamp":" 947332413560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332414534","data":{"timestamp":" 947332414534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332415208","data":{"timestamp":" 947332415208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332418458","data":{"timestamp":" 947332418458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332419823","data":{"timestamp":" 947332419822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332420057","data":{"timestamp":" 947332420057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332420442","data":{"timestamp":" 947332420441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332421287","data":{"timestamp":" 947332421287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332422619","data":{"timestamp":" 947332422618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332424245","data":{"timestamp":" 947332424244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332424495","data":{"timestamp":" 947332424494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332425568","data":{"timestamp":" 947332425567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332427159","data":{"timestamp":" 947332427158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332428671","data":{"timestamp":" 947332428671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332429464","data":{"timestamp":" 947332429463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332429573","data":{"timestamp":" 947332429572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332430244","data":{"timestamp":" 947332430244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332431141","data":{"timestamp":" 947332431141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332433192","data":{"timestamp":" 947332433191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAAMINI"," userResponse":" NAAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332433435","data":{"timestamp":" 947332433435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332434174","data":{"timestamp":" 947332434173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332435090","data":{"timestamp":" 947332435090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332435316","data":{"timestamp":" 947332435316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332436560","data":{"timestamp":" 947332436560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332439077","data":{"timestamp":" 947332439077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332439494","data":{"timestamp":" 947332439494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332440190","data":{"timestamp":" 947332440189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332441109","data":{"timestamp":" 947332441108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWITA"," userResponse":" ALIMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332442142","data":{"timestamp":" 947332442142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332443347","data":{"timestamp":" 947332443345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332444022","data":{"timestamp":" 947332444021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332445217","data":{"timestamp":" 947332445216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEJAA"," userResponse":" KIMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332445872","data":{"timestamp":" 947332445871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332446709","data":{"timestamp":" 947332446709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332446870","data":{"timestamp":" 947332446870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332447904","data":{"timestamp":" 947332447904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332450126","data":{"timestamp":" 947332450125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332450643","data":{"timestamp":" 947332450642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332451473","data":{"timestamp":" 947332451472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332454434","data":{"timestamp":" 947332454433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332455145","data":{"timestamp":" 947332455144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332455763","data":{"timestamp":" 947332455762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332456626","data":{"timestamp":" 947332456626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332457665","data":{"timestamp":" 947332457665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332459896","data":{"timestamp":" 947332459895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332460343","data":{"timestamp":" 947332460342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332461341","data":{"timestamp":" 947332461341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332462512","data":{"timestamp":" 947332462512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332463662","data":{"timestamp":" 947332463661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHAURI"," userResponse":" ALISHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332464454","data":{"timestamp":" 947332464454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332465961","data":{"timestamp":" 947332465960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASOKOTE"," userResponse":" ASOKOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332466895","data":{"timestamp":" 947332466895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332468232","data":{"timestamp":" 947332468231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332468765","data":{"timestamp":" 947332468765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332469396","data":{"timestamp":" 947332469395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332470258","data":{"timestamp":" 947332470258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332471096","data":{"timestamp":" 947332471095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332471735","data":{"timestamp":" 947332471735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332472300","data":{"timestamp":" 947332472299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332473077","data":{"timestamp":" 947332473077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332473600","data":{"timestamp":" 947332473600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332474201","data":{"timestamp":" 947332474200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332474417","data":{"timestamp":" 947332474417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332475104","data":{"timestamp":" 947332475104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332475952","data":{"timestamp":" 947332475952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332478411","data":{"timestamp":" 947332478410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332478789","data":{"timestamp":" 947332478789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332479457","data":{"timestamp":" 947332479456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332480251","data":{"timestamp":" 947332480251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONA"," userResponse":" AKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332480499","data":{"timestamp":" 947332480498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332480988","data":{"timestamp":" 947332480988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332481821","data":{"timestamp":" 947332481820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332482603","data":{"timestamp":" 947332482602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332483667","data":{"timestamp":" 947332483666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332484268","data":{"timestamp":" 947332484268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332487555","data":{"timestamp":" 947332487554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332488314","data":{"timestamp":" 947332488313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332489303","data":{"timestamp":" 947332489302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332490186","data":{"timestamp":" 947332490185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332491251","data":{"timestamp":" 947332491248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332491748","data":{"timestamp":" 947332491748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332492831","data":{"timestamp":" 947332492830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332493998","data":{"timestamp":" 947332493997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332495358","data":{"timestamp":" 947332495358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332495718","data":{"timestamp":" 947332495717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332496411","data":{"timestamp":" 947332496410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332496714","data":{"timestamp":" 947332496713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332497758","data":{"timestamp":" 947332497757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332500360","data":{"timestamp":" 947332500360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332501889","data":{"timestamp":" 947332501889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJISEMEA"," userResponse":" AKAJISEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332503101","data":{"timestamp":" 947332503100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332503410","data":{"timestamp":" 947332503409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332504430","data":{"timestamp":" 947332504429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIVUNO"," userResponse":" MAJIVUNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332505354","data":{"timestamp":" 947332505353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332506336","data":{"timestamp":" 947332506335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332506568","data":{"timestamp":" 947332506567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332507038","data":{"timestamp":" 947332507038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332507768","data":{"timestamp":" 947332507767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332508296","data":{"timestamp":" 947332508295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332510051","data":{"timestamp":" 947332510050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" NAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332510602","data":{"timestamp":" 947332510602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332511465","data":{"timestamp":" 947332511465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332511713","data":{"timestamp":" 947332511712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332512752","data":{"timestamp":" 947332512751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAIVA"," userResponse":" KITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332514135","data":{"timestamp":" 947332514135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332516105","data":{"timestamp":" 947332516105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332516656","data":{"timestamp":" 947332516656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332517484","data":{"timestamp":" 947332517483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332518398","data":{"timestamp":" 947332518397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332518902","data":{"timestamp":" 947332518901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332520426","data":{"timestamp":" 947332520426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEVUTWA"," userResponse":" UMEVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332522991","data":{"timestamp":" 947332522991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332523469","data":{"timestamp":" 947332523468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AH"," userResponse":" AH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332524886","data":{"timestamp":" 947332524886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332525293","data":{"timestamp":" 947332525293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332525741","data":{"timestamp":" 947332525740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332526070","data":{"timestamp":" 947332526069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332527061","data":{"timestamp":" 947332527061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332528453","data":{"timestamp":" 947332528452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUNGWA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332529517","data":{"timestamp":" 947332529517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332530233","data":{"timestamp":" 947332530232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332530468","data":{"timestamp":" 947332530468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332531243","data":{"timestamp":" 947332531242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332531520","data":{"timestamp":" 947332531518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332532131","data":{"timestamp":" 947332532130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332532354","data":{"timestamp":" 947332532353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332533261","data":{"timestamp":" 947332533260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332536328","data":{"timestamp":" 947332536327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332536919","data":{"timestamp":" 947332536918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUTO"," userResponse":" MVUTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332537771","data":{"timestamp":" 947332537769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332538693","data":{"timestamp":" 947332538692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332539628","data":{"timestamp":" 947332539628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332542393","data":{"timestamp":" 947332542393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332543591","data":{"timestamp":" 947332543590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTWA"," userResponse":" ALIVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332544129","data":{"timestamp":" 947332544128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANDE"," userResponse":" PANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332545031","data":{"timestamp":" 947332545030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332545955","data":{"timestamp":" 947332545955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332546608","data":{"timestamp":" 947332546608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332547323","data":{"timestamp":" 947332547322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332549497","data":{"timestamp":" 947332549497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332550630","data":{"timestamp":" 947332550630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMANI"," userResponse":" JAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332551820","data":{"timestamp":" 947332551820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332552871","data":{"timestamp":" 947332552871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332553733","data":{"timestamp":" 947332553732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332554084","data":{"timestamp":" 947332554083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332554946","data":{"timestamp":" 947332554945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTWA"," userResponse":" KUVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332555218","data":{"timestamp":" 947332555217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332555760","data":{"timestamp":" 947332555759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332555978","data":{"timestamp":" 947332555978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332556590","data":{"timestamp":" 947332556589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332559184","data":{"timestamp":" 947332559184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332559823","data":{"timestamp":" 947332559822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332560314","data":{"timestamp":" 947332560313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332561638","data":{"timestamp":" 947332561637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332562148","data":{"timestamp":" 947332562147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332562370","data":{"timestamp":" 947332562369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332563045","data":{"timestamp":" 947332563045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332564099","data":{"timestamp":" 947332564099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAVUTWA"," userResponse":" INAVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332564814","data":{"timestamp":" 947332564814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332565036","data":{"timestamp":" 947332565035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332565692","data":{"timestamp":" 947332565691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332566586","data":{"timestamp":" 947332566586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332566858","data":{"timestamp":" 947332566857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332567587","data":{"timestamp":" 947332567587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332568401","data":{"timestamp":" 947332568400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332568682","data":{"timestamp":" 947332568682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332569436","data":{"timestamp":" 947332569435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332572019","data":{"timestamp":" 947332572017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332573311","data":{"timestamp":" 947332573310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTWA"," userResponse":" ALIVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332574197","data":{"timestamp":" 947332574196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332574565","data":{"timestamp":" 947332574564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332575084","data":{"timestamp":" 947332575084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332575903","data":{"timestamp":" 947332575903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332576183","data":{"timestamp":" 947332576182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332578819","data":{"timestamp":" 947332578818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332579305","data":{"timestamp":" 947332579305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332580286","data":{"timestamp":" 947332580284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAVUTA"," userResponse":" AKAVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332580752","data":{"timestamp":" 947332580752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILE"," userResponse":" ZILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332581455","data":{"timestamp":" 947332581454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332582038","data":{"timestamp":" 947332582037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332582649","data":{"timestamp":" 947332582649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332583570","data":{"timestamp":" 947332583570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332586081","data":{"timestamp":" 947332586080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332586618","data":{"timestamp":" 947332586618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332587877","data":{"timestamp":" 947332587876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAVUTWA"," userResponse":" IKAVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332588688","data":{"timestamp":" 947332588687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332589922","data":{"timestamp":" 947332589921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332590289","data":{"timestamp":" 947332590289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332591549","data":{"timestamp":" 947332591549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332594910","data":{"timestamp":" 947332594910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332596441","data":{"timestamp":" 947332596440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIRUSHA"," userResponse":" AKAJIRUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332596990","data":{"timestamp":" 947332596989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332597612","data":{"timestamp":" 947332597611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332600425","data":{"timestamp":" 947332600424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332601021","data":{"timestamp":" 947332601020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANDO"," userResponse":" TANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332601596","data":{"timestamp":" 947332601595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332602928","data":{"timestamp":" 947332602927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMECHUKULIWA"," userResponse":" ZIMECHUKULIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332603204","data":{"timestamp":" 947332603204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332604085","data":{"timestamp":" 947332604084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332605830","data":{"timestamp":" 947332605830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIVUTA"," userResponse":" ALIJIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332607444","data":{"timestamp":" 947332607443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" TARATIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332608107","data":{"timestamp":" 947332608107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332609742","data":{"timestamp":" 947332609742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMIVU"," userResponse":" MAUMIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332610828","data":{"timestamp":" 947332610827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332611373","data":{"timestamp":" 947332611372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332612260","data":{"timestamp":" 947332612260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UFUKWE"," userResponse":" UFUKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332614691","data":{"timestamp":" 947332614690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332616360","data":{"timestamp":" 947332616360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAHEMA"," userResponse":" AKAHEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332617224","data":{"timestamp":" 947332617220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332618436","data":{"timestamp":" 947332618435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJONZI"," userResponse":" MAJONZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332619421","data":{"timestamp":" 947332619421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332620236","data":{"timestamp":" 947332620236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332621070","data":{"timestamp":" 947332621070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332621845","data":{"timestamp":" 947332621845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332623060","data":{"timestamp":" 947332623060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGINE"," userResponse":" PENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332623675","data":{"timestamp":" 947332623674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332624739","data":{"timestamp":" 947332624739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUWA"," userResponse":" HALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332625384","data":{"timestamp":" 947332625383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332625974","data":{"timestamp":" 947332625974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332626690","data":{"timestamp":" 947332626690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332628930","data":{"timestamp":" 947332628930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332629590","data":{"timestamp":" 947332629589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332630201","data":{"timestamp":" 947332630200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332631592","data":{"timestamp":" 947332631591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332632781","data":{"timestamp":" 947332632780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332633552","data":{"timestamp":" 947332633552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332634213","data":{"timestamp":" 947332634212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332635317","data":{"timestamp":" 947332635317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINANE"," userResponse":" MINANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332636828","data":{"timestamp":" 947332636828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332637972","data":{"timestamp":" 947332637972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332640127","data":{"timestamp":" 947332640127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332641079","data":{"timestamp":" 947332641078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332641826","data":{"timestamp":" 947332641825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332642929","data":{"timestamp":" 947332642928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUPATA"," userResponse":" HAKUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332643708","data":{"timestamp":" 947332643707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332644527","data":{"timestamp":" 947332644526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332647307","data":{"timestamp":" 947332647306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332647436","data":{"timestamp":" 947332647435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332664194","data":{"timestamp":" 947332664194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 466522c0-f34f-448d-ba3e-232fa40c7e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332687192","data":{"timestamp":" 947332687191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332689589","data":{"timestamp":" 947332689588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332691222","data":{"timestamp":" 947332691221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332694663","data":{"timestamp":" 947332694662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" START_WANAWAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332697000","data":{"timestamp":" 947332697000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332698593","data":{"timestamp":" 947332698593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" WALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332701164","data":{"timestamp":" 947332701163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" WALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332702775","data":{"timestamp":" 947332702774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332705209","data":{"timestamp":" 947332705208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332706831","data":{"timestamp":" 947332706830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332709485","data":{"timestamp":" 947332709484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332711110","data":{"timestamp":" 947332711110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332716301","data":{"timestamp":" 947332716300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332717935","data":{"timestamp":" 947332717934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332721119","data":{"timestamp":" 947332721118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332722752","data":{"timestamp":" 947332722751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wadudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332725342","data":{"timestamp":" 947332725341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wadudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332726975","data":{"timestamp":" 947332726974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" WAKIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332729602","data":{"timestamp":" 947332729602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" START_WAKIRUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332732416","data":{"timestamp":" 947332732415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" START_WAKIRUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332734121","data":{"timestamp":" 947332734120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332735743","data":{"timestamp":" 947332735743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332740884","data":{"timestamp":" 947332740883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332742916","data":{"timestamp":" 947332742914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332743027","data":{"timestamp":" 947332743027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 242500ab-3f91-4807-815e-ce23467fb028"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332757839","data":{"timestamp":" 947332757838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332760814","data":{"timestamp":" 947332760813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332762430","data":{"timestamp":" 947332762430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332765387","data":{"timestamp":" 947332765387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332767004","data":{"timestamp":" 947332767003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" WALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332769617","data":{"timestamp":" 947332769616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" START_WALIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332771919","data":{"timestamp":" 947332771919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" START_WALIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332773454","data":{"timestamp":" 947332773454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332774127","data":{"timestamp":" 947332774127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" START_WALIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332775193","data":{"timestamp":" 947332775192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332787454","data":{"timestamp":" 947332787453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332789063","data":{"timestamp":" 947332789062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332791746","data":{"timestamp":" 947332791746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332793350","data":{"timestamp":" 947332793349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332796001","data":{"timestamp":" 947332796000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332797615","data":{"timestamp":" 947332797614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332800327","data":{"timestamp":" 947332800327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" START_WAKULIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332806440","data":{"timestamp":" 947332806439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" START_WAKULIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332808226","data":{"timestamp":" 947332808225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332809847","data":{"timestamp":" 947332809846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wadudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332812922","data":{"timestamp":" 947332812920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wadudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332814516","data":{"timestamp":" 947332814515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" WAKIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332822285","data":{"timestamp":" 947332822284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332823890","data":{"timestamp":" 947332823890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332829340","data":{"timestamp":" 947332829340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" START_WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332832792","data":{"timestamp":" 947332832791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332834826","data":{"timestamp":" 947332834825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332835061","data":{"timestamp":" 947332835060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" b01b8ee4-a57e-447a-b091-70bfafe41311"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332850342","data":{"timestamp":" 947332850342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 964541b0-58c5-4c6c-b609-d1d7e15ffdaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_w-y-j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332855499","data":{"timestamp":" 947332855499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 964541b0-58c5-4c6c-b609-d1d7e15ffdaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_i-w-h"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332858663","data":{"timestamp":" 947332858663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 964541b0-58c5-4c6c-b609-d1d7e15ffdaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_f-w-b"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332862363","data":{"timestamp":" 947332862363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 964541b0-58c5-4c6c-b609-d1d7e15ffdaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_z-i-w"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332866465","data":{"timestamp":" 947332866465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 964541b0-58c5-4c6c-b609-d1d7e15ffdaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_r-i-w"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332876443","data":{"timestamp":" 947332876443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 964541b0-58c5-4c6c-b609-d1d7e15ffdaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_p-j-w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332881202","data":{"timestamp":" 947332881202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 964541b0-58c5-4c6c-b609-d1d7e15ffdaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_a-e-w"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332884868","data":{"timestamp":" 947332884868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 964541b0-58c5-4c6c-b609-d1d7e15ffdaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_w-z-n"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332890395","data":{"timestamp":" 947332890394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 964541b0-58c5-4c6c-b609-d1d7e15ffdaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_w-t-o"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332896595","data":{"timestamp":" 947332896595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 964541b0-58c5-4c6c-b609-d1d7e15ffdaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_ch-b-w"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332902341","data":{"timestamp":" 947332902341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 964541b0-58c5-4c6c-b609-d1d7e15ffdaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_w_ch-b-w"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332943015","data":{"timestamp":" 947332943014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" bfd38e3d-e95d-43cb-8f58-38c62e4d3c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_p_l"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332949695","data":{"timestamp":" 947332949695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" bfd38e3d-e95d-43cb-8f58-38c62e4d3c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_r_n"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332956333","data":{"timestamp":" 947332956332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" bfd38e3d-e95d-43cb-8f58-38c62e4d3c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_w_u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332962946","data":{"timestamp":" 947332962945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" bfd38e3d-e95d-43cb-8f58-38c62e4d3c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_m_h_w"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332969619","data":{"timestamp":" 947332969618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" bfd38e3d-e95d-43cb-8f58-38c62e4d3c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_w_t"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332976261","data":{"timestamp":" 947332976260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" bfd38e3d-e95d-43cb-8f58-38c62e4d3c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_w_j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332982920","data":{"timestamp":" 947332982919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" bfd38e3d-e95d-43cb-8f58-38c62e4d3c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_m_w_o"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332989599","data":{"timestamp":" 947332989598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" bfd38e3d-e95d-43cb-8f58-38c62e4d3c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_r"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947332996269","data":{"timestamp":" 947332996269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" bfd38e3d-e95d-43cb-8f58-38c62e4d3c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_h_w"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333003765","data":{"timestamp":" 947333003763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" bfd38e3d-e95d-43cb-8f58-38c62e4d3c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_h_w"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:W..W.all.10.rand.say.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333011660","data":{"timestamp":" 947333011660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" bfd38e3d-e95d-43cb-8f58-38c62e4d3c20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_W..W.all.10.rand.say.60"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_b_h_w"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333035370","data":{"timestamp":" 947333035369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333036009","data":{"timestamp":" 947333036008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333036271","data":{"timestamp":" 947333036271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333036842","data":{"timestamp":" 947333036842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333038002","data":{"timestamp":" 947333038002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333038770","data":{"timestamp":" 947333038770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333040188","data":{"timestamp":" 947333040187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333041088","data":{"timestamp":" 947333041087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333041725","data":{"timestamp":" 947333041724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333042667","data":{"timestamp":" 947333042666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333043319","data":{"timestamp":" 947333043318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333045743","data":{"timestamp":" 947333045743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333045998","data":{"timestamp":" 947333045998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333046938","data":{"timestamp":" 947333046938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333047827","data":{"timestamp":" 947333047827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333048677","data":{"timestamp":" 947333048676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPISHI"," userResponse":" MPISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333049583","data":{"timestamp":" 947333049582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333052358","data":{"timestamp":" 947333052357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333052782","data":{"timestamp":" 947333052782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333053476","data":{"timestamp":" 947333053476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333054541","data":{"timestamp":" 947333054541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333055481","data":{"timestamp":" 947333055480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333056312","data":{"timestamp":" 947333056311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONJA"," userResponse":" KUONJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333057262","data":{"timestamp":" 947333057261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333058887","data":{"timestamp":" 947333058887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333059085","data":{"timestamp":" 947333059084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333059929","data":{"timestamp":" 947333059929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333060623","data":{"timestamp":" 947333060623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333060917","data":{"timestamp":" 947333060917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333061781","data":{"timestamp":" 947333061781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333062855","data":{"timestamp":" 947333062854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333065951","data":{"timestamp":" 947333065950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333066566","data":{"timestamp":" 947333066566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333067678","data":{"timestamp":" 947333067677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333068830","data":{"timestamp":" 947333068829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPITA"," userResponse":" ALIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333069191","data":{"timestamp":" 947333069190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333070073","data":{"timestamp":" 947333070072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333071317","data":{"timestamp":" 947333071316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" RAFIKIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333072141","data":{"timestamp":" 947333072141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333074766","data":{"timestamp":" 947333074765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333075668","data":{"timestamp":" 947333075667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333076243","data":{"timestamp":" 947333076243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333076489","data":{"timestamp":" 947333076488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333077221","data":{"timestamp":" 947333077221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333078042","data":{"timestamp":" 947333078042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333080627","data":{"timestamp":" 947333080627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333081627","data":{"timestamp":" 947333081627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333082092","data":{"timestamp":" 947333082092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333082347","data":{"timestamp":" 947333082347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333083122","data":{"timestamp":" 947333083122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333084407","data":{"timestamp":" 947333084407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333084722","data":{"timestamp":" 947333084722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333085961","data":{"timestamp":" 947333085960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMUKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333086880","data":{"timestamp":" 947333086879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333087543","data":{"timestamp":" 947333087542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333087797","data":{"timestamp":" 947333087796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333088664","data":{"timestamp":" 947333088664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333089207","data":{"timestamp":" 947333089206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333089792","data":{"timestamp":" 947333089791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333090347","data":{"timestamp":" 947333090347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333093111","data":{"timestamp":" 947333093111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333094366","data":{"timestamp":" 947333094366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333095369","data":{"timestamp":" 947333095369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333096713","data":{"timestamp":" 947333096713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAZIJAIVA"," userResponse":" HAZIJAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333097748","data":{"timestamp":" 947333097748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333098273","data":{"timestamp":" 947333098272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333099434","data":{"timestamp":" 947333099434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBUNI"," userResponse":" KARIBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333100886","data":{"timestamp":" 947333100885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333102033","data":{"timestamp":" 947333102032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRI"," userResponse":" SUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333102583","data":{"timestamp":" 947333102583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333103550","data":{"timestamp":" 947333103550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333106174","data":{"timestamp":" 947333106173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333107154","data":{"timestamp":" 947333107154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333107461","data":{"timestamp":" 947333107460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333108236","data":{"timestamp":" 947333108235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333109611","data":{"timestamp":" 947333109610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333110283","data":{"timestamp":" 947333110282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333110713","data":{"timestamp":" 947333110713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333111566","data":{"timestamp":" 947333111566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333112609","data":{"timestamp":" 947333112609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333113089","data":{"timestamp":" 947333113089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333114037","data":{"timestamp":" 947333114037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJUKUMU"," userResponse":" MAJUKUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333114238","data":{"timestamp":" 947333114237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333115020","data":{"timestamp":" 947333115019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333117652","data":{"timestamp":" 947333117651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333118663","data":{"timestamp":" 947333118662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333119637","data":{"timestamp":" 947333119636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESUBIRI"," userResponse":" ANGESUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333120872","data":{"timestamp":" 947333120871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333121510","data":{"timestamp":" 947333121510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333122645","data":{"timestamp":" 947333122645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333123459","data":{"timestamp":" 947333123459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMPA"," userResponse":" ANGEMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333124194","data":{"timestamp":" 947333124194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333124348","data":{"timestamp":" 947333124347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333125102","data":{"timestamp":" 947333125102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333128311","data":{"timestamp":" 947333128311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333129586","data":{"timestamp":" 947333129586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWABIA"," userResponse":" AKAMWABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333130420","data":{"timestamp":" 947333130420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333132604","data":{"timestamp":" 947333132604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITASOKOTA"," userResponse":" NITASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333133468","data":{"timestamp":" 947333133468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333134692","data":{"timestamp":" 947333134692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFUNGE"," userResponse":" NIFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333135366","data":{"timestamp":" 947333135366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333135920","data":{"timestamp":" 947333135920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333136545","data":{"timestamp":" 947333136545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333137563","data":{"timestamp":" 947333137563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333137960","data":{"timestamp":" 947333137959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333138689","data":{"timestamp":" 947333138688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333139174","data":{"timestamp":" 947333139174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333139619","data":{"timestamp":" 947333139619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333140225","data":{"timestamp":" 947333140225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333142774","data":{"timestamp":" 947333142773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333144448","data":{"timestamp":" 947333144448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333145593","data":{"timestamp":" 947333145593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUTA"," userResponse":" VUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333146356","data":{"timestamp":" 947333146356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333146820","data":{"timestamp":" 947333146820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333147886","data":{"timestamp":" 947333147886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKIMBIA"," userResponse":" NITAKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333148440","data":{"timestamp":" 947333148440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJE"," userResponse":" NIJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333151146","data":{"timestamp":" 947333151146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333152050","data":{"timestamp":" 947333152050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333152754","data":{"timestamp":" 947333152754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333152928","data":{"timestamp":" 947333152928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333153442","data":{"timestamp":" 947333153442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333154156","data":{"timestamp":" 947333154156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333154709","data":{"timestamp":" 947333154709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333157629","data":{"timestamp":" 947333157629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333158243","data":{"timestamp":" 947333158242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333161443","data":{"timestamp":" 947333161443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333162828","data":{"timestamp":" 947333162827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333163101","data":{"timestamp":" 947333163101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333163955","data":{"timestamp":" 947333163955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333165210","data":{"timestamp":" 947333165209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333166073","data":{"timestamp":" 947333166073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333166167","data":{"timestamp":" 947333166167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333166502","data":{"timestamp":" 947333166502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333167546","data":{"timestamp":" 947333167546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333168481","data":{"timestamp":" 947333168481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333170455","data":{"timestamp":" 947333170455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333171290","data":{"timestamp":" 947333171290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333171396","data":{"timestamp":" 947333171396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333172373","data":{"timestamp":" 947333172373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333173829","data":{"timestamp":" 947333173829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333174876","data":{"timestamp":" 947333174876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333176422","data":{"timestamp":" 947333176422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPIKWA"," userResponse":" YANAPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333176958","data":{"timestamp":" 947333176958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333177694","data":{"timestamp":" 947333177694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333180904","data":{"timestamp":" 947333180904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333182129","data":{"timestamp":" 947333182129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWITA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333182923","data":{"timestamp":" 947333182923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333184018","data":{"timestamp":" 947333184018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333184603","data":{"timestamp":" 947333184603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333185568","data":{"timestamp":" 947333185568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333186413","data":{"timestamp":" 947333186413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333187519","data":{"timestamp":" 947333187518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333188602","data":{"timestamp":" 947333188602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATAIVA"," userResponse":" YATAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333191341","data":{"timestamp":" 947333191341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333192344","data":{"timestamp":" 947333192344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333194029","data":{"timestamp":" 947333194029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333194654","data":{"timestamp":" 947333194654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333195047","data":{"timestamp":" 947333195047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333195861","data":{"timestamp":" 947333195861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333198691","data":{"timestamp":" 947333198691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333199867","data":{"timestamp":" 947333199867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHAURI"," userResponse":" AKASHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333200461","data":{"timestamp":" 947333200461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333201294","data":{"timestamp":" 947333201294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333202570","data":{"timestamp":" 947333202570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATASOKOTA"," userResponse":" ATASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333203434","data":{"timestamp":" 947333203434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333204551","data":{"timestamp":" 947333204550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333205025","data":{"timestamp":" 947333205025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333205611","data":{"timestamp":" 947333205611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333206466","data":{"timestamp":" 947333206466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333207101","data":{"timestamp":" 947333207101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333207747","data":{"timestamp":" 947333207746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333208252","data":{"timestamp":" 947333208251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333208988","data":{"timestamp":" 947333208988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333209453","data":{"timestamp":" 947333209453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333209968","data":{"timestamp":" 947333209968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333210944","data":{"timestamp":" 947333210944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333211201","data":{"timestamp":" 947333211201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333212083","data":{"timestamp":" 947333212083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333214390","data":{"timestamp":" 947333214390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333215252","data":{"timestamp":" 947333215252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333216192","data":{"timestamp":" 947333216191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333216825","data":{"timestamp":" 947333216825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333217055","data":{"timestamp":" 947333217055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333217999","data":{"timestamp":" 947333217999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333219151","data":{"timestamp":" 947333219151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333219686","data":{"timestamp":" 947333219686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333220470","data":{"timestamp":" 947333220470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333221245","data":{"timestamp":" 947333221245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333221820","data":{"timestamp":" 947333221819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333222655","data":{"timestamp":" 947333222654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333223519","data":{"timestamp":" 947333223519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333224355","data":{"timestamp":" 947333224355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" WAKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333225049","data":{"timestamp":" 947333225049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333227206","data":{"timestamp":" 947333227205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333227767","data":{"timestamp":" 947333227764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333228762","data":{"timestamp":" 947333228759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333229455","data":{"timestamp":" 947333229455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333232777","data":{"timestamp":" 947333232777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333234141","data":{"timestamp":" 947333234141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333234376","data":{"timestamp":" 947333234376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333234761","data":{"timestamp":" 947333234761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333235585","data":{"timestamp":" 947333235585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333236918","data":{"timestamp":" 947333236917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333238541","data":{"timestamp":" 947333238540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333238791","data":{"timestamp":" 947333238791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333239866","data":{"timestamp":" 947333239865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333241441","data":{"timestamp":" 947333241441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333242936","data":{"timestamp":" 947333242936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333243711","data":{"timestamp":" 947333243711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333243817","data":{"timestamp":" 947333243817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333244473","data":{"timestamp":" 947333244473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333245349","data":{"timestamp":" 947333245349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333247373","data":{"timestamp":" 947333247373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAAMINI"," userResponse":" NAAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333247598","data":{"timestamp":" 947333247598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333248315","data":{"timestamp":" 947333248314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333249211","data":{"timestamp":" 947333249210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333249417","data":{"timestamp":" 947333249417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333250674","data":{"timestamp":" 947333250673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333253323","data":{"timestamp":" 947333253323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333253728","data":{"timestamp":" 947333253728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333254429","data":{"timestamp":" 947333254428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333255345","data":{"timestamp":" 947333255345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWITA"," userResponse":" ALIMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333256376","data":{"timestamp":" 947333256375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333257568","data":{"timestamp":" 947333257568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333258234","data":{"timestamp":" 947333258234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333259410","data":{"timestamp":" 947333259410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEJAA"," userResponse":" KIMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333260045","data":{"timestamp":" 947333260045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333260860","data":{"timestamp":" 947333260860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333261005","data":{"timestamp":" 947333261005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333262020","data":{"timestamp":" 947333262020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333264331","data":{"timestamp":" 947333264330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333264835","data":{"timestamp":" 947333264834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333265648","data":{"timestamp":" 947333265648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333268560","data":{"timestamp":" 947333268560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333269254","data":{"timestamp":" 947333269254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333269858","data":{"timestamp":" 947333269858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333270702","data":{"timestamp":" 947333270702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333271726","data":{"timestamp":" 947333271726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333273925","data":{"timestamp":" 947333273925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333274360","data":{"timestamp":" 947333274360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333275345","data":{"timestamp":" 947333275345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333276489","data":{"timestamp":" 947333276488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333277623","data":{"timestamp":" 947333277623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHAURI"," userResponse":" ALISHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333278398","data":{"timestamp":" 947333278398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333279903","data":{"timestamp":" 947333279902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASOKOTE"," userResponse":" ASOKOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333280834","data":{"timestamp":" 947333280833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333282163","data":{"timestamp":" 947333282162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333282693","data":{"timestamp":" 947333282692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333283332","data":{"timestamp":" 947333283331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333284197","data":{"timestamp":" 947333284197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333285033","data":{"timestamp":" 947333285032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333285676","data":{"timestamp":" 947333285676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333286242","data":{"timestamp":" 947333286241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333287020","data":{"timestamp":" 947333287020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333287543","data":{"timestamp":" 947333287542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333288137","data":{"timestamp":" 947333288137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333288352","data":{"timestamp":" 947333288352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333289040","data":{"timestamp":" 947333289040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333289883","data":{"timestamp":" 947333289883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333292375","data":{"timestamp":" 947333292374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333292756","data":{"timestamp":" 947333292755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333293421","data":{"timestamp":" 947333293420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333294213","data":{"timestamp":" 947333294212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONA"," userResponse":" AKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333294462","data":{"timestamp":" 947333294462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333294953","data":{"timestamp":" 947333294952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333295787","data":{"timestamp":" 947333295787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333296567","data":{"timestamp":" 947333296566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333297629","data":{"timestamp":" 947333297629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333298228","data":{"timestamp":" 947333298228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333301521","data":{"timestamp":" 947333301520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333302280","data":{"timestamp":" 947333302279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333303269","data":{"timestamp":" 947333303268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333304151","data":{"timestamp":" 947333304151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333305213","data":{"timestamp":" 947333305210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333305712","data":{"timestamp":" 947333305712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333306794","data":{"timestamp":" 947333306794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333307966","data":{"timestamp":" 947333307965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333309312","data":{"timestamp":" 947333309312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333309658","data":{"timestamp":" 947333309657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333310351","data":{"timestamp":" 947333310351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333310649","data":{"timestamp":" 947333310649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333311694","data":{"timestamp":" 947333311693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333314356","data":{"timestamp":" 947333314356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333315886","data":{"timestamp":" 947333315886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJISEMEA"," userResponse":" AKAJISEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333317081","data":{"timestamp":" 947333317081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333317374","data":{"timestamp":" 947333317374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333318393","data":{"timestamp":" 947333318393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIVUNO"," userResponse":" MAJIVUNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333319313","data":{"timestamp":" 947333319312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333320296","data":{"timestamp":" 947333320295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333320523","data":{"timestamp":" 947333320523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333320993","data":{"timestamp":" 947333320992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333321698","data":{"timestamp":" 947333321697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333322212","data":{"timestamp":" 947333322211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333323946","data":{"timestamp":" 947333323946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" NAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333324481","data":{"timestamp":" 947333324481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333325355","data":{"timestamp":" 947333325354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333325608","data":{"timestamp":" 947333325607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333326641","data":{"timestamp":" 947333326640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAIVA"," userResponse":" KITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333328026","data":{"timestamp":" 947333328025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333330109","data":{"timestamp":" 947333330108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333330658","data":{"timestamp":" 947333330657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333331489","data":{"timestamp":" 947333331488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333332383","data":{"timestamp":" 947333332383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333332878","data":{"timestamp":" 947333332877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333334393","data":{"timestamp":" 947333334392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEVUTWA"," userResponse":" UMEVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333336874","data":{"timestamp":" 947333336873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333337354","data":{"timestamp":" 947333337353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AH"," userResponse":" AH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333338775","data":{"timestamp":" 947333338775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333339183","data":{"timestamp":" 947333339182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333339634","data":{"timestamp":" 947333339633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333339949","data":{"timestamp":" 947333339948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333340923","data":{"timestamp":" 947333340922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333342312","data":{"timestamp":" 947333342311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUNGWA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333343383","data":{"timestamp":" 947333343382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333344106","data":{"timestamp":" 947333344105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333344342","data":{"timestamp":" 947333344342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333345116","data":{"timestamp":" 947333345115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333345387","data":{"timestamp":" 947333345387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333346001","data":{"timestamp":" 947333346000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333346224","data":{"timestamp":" 947333346223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333347133","data":{"timestamp":" 947333347132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333350166","data":{"timestamp":" 947333350165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333350757","data":{"timestamp":" 947333350756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUTO"," userResponse":" MVUTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333351609","data":{"timestamp":" 947333351608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333352529","data":{"timestamp":" 947333352528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333353460","data":{"timestamp":" 947333353459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333356237","data":{"timestamp":" 947333356236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333357411","data":{"timestamp":" 947333357411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTWA"," userResponse":" ALIVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333357935","data":{"timestamp":" 947333357935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANDE"," userResponse":" PANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333358819","data":{"timestamp":" 947333358819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333359740","data":{"timestamp":" 947333359739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333360402","data":{"timestamp":" 947333360402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333361114","data":{"timestamp":" 947333361114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333363327","data":{"timestamp":" 947333363327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333364457","data":{"timestamp":" 947333364456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMANI"," userResponse":" JAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333365648","data":{"timestamp":" 947333365647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333366698","data":{"timestamp":" 947333366697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333367561","data":{"timestamp":" 947333367560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333367913","data":{"timestamp":" 947333367911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333368775","data":{"timestamp":" 947333368774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTWA"," userResponse":" KUVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333369046","data":{"timestamp":" 947333369045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333369592","data":{"timestamp":" 947333369591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333369802","data":{"timestamp":" 947333369801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333370415","data":{"timestamp":" 947333370414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333373027","data":{"timestamp":" 947333373026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333373664","data":{"timestamp":" 947333373663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333374149","data":{"timestamp":" 947333374149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333375454","data":{"timestamp":" 947333375454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333375949","data":{"timestamp":" 947333375949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333376154","data":{"timestamp":" 947333376153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333376808","data":{"timestamp":" 947333376808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333377841","data":{"timestamp":" 947333377841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAVUTWA"," userResponse":" INAVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333378536","data":{"timestamp":" 947333378536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333378741","data":{"timestamp":" 947333378741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333379376","data":{"timestamp":" 947333379376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333380252","data":{"timestamp":" 947333380251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333380506","data":{"timestamp":" 947333380506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333381221","data":{"timestamp":" 947333381221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333382016","data":{"timestamp":" 947333382016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333382281","data":{"timestamp":" 947333382280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333383005","data":{"timestamp":" 947333383005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333385708","data":{"timestamp":" 947333385708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333386996","data":{"timestamp":" 947333386996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTWA"," userResponse":" ALIVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333387888","data":{"timestamp":" 947333387888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333388257","data":{"timestamp":" 947333388256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333388776","data":{"timestamp":" 947333388775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333389597","data":{"timestamp":" 947333389597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333389878","data":{"timestamp":" 947333389877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333392427","data":{"timestamp":" 947333392427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333392900","data":{"timestamp":" 947333392900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333393864","data":{"timestamp":" 947333393864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAVUTA"," userResponse":" AKAVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333394318","data":{"timestamp":" 947333394318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILE"," userResponse":" ZILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333395003","data":{"timestamp":" 947333395003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333395566","data":{"timestamp":" 947333395566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333396150","data":{"timestamp":" 947333396150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333397055","data":{"timestamp":" 947333397055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333399624","data":{"timestamp":" 947333399624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333400149","data":{"timestamp":" 947333400149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333401394","data":{"timestamp":" 947333401394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAVUTWA"," userResponse":" IKAVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333402190","data":{"timestamp":" 947333402189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333403403","data":{"timestamp":" 947333403403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333403758","data":{"timestamp":" 947333403758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333405004","data":{"timestamp":" 947333405004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333408332","data":{"timestamp":" 947333408332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333409846","data":{"timestamp":" 947333409846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIRUSHA"," userResponse":" AKAJIRUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333410380","data":{"timestamp":" 947333410380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333410984","data":{"timestamp":" 947333410984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333413732","data":{"timestamp":" 947333413731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333414306","data":{"timestamp":" 947333414305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANDO"," userResponse":" TANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333414869","data":{"timestamp":" 947333414869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333416184","data":{"timestamp":" 947333416184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMECHUKULIWA"," userResponse":" ZIMECHUKULIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333416448","data":{"timestamp":" 947333416448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333417301","data":{"timestamp":" 947333417301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333419026","data":{"timestamp":" 947333419026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIVUTA"," userResponse":" ALIJIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333420621","data":{"timestamp":" 947333420621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" TARATIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333421266","data":{"timestamp":" 947333421266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333422881","data":{"timestamp":" 947333422881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMIVU"," userResponse":" MAUMIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333423947","data":{"timestamp":" 947333423946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333424471","data":{"timestamp":" 947333424471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333425336","data":{"timestamp":" 947333425336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UFUKWE"," userResponse":" UFUKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333427914","data":{"timestamp":" 947333427913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333429567","data":{"timestamp":" 947333429566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAHEMA"," userResponse":" AKAHEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333430413","data":{"timestamp":" 947333430413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333431608","data":{"timestamp":" 947333431608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJONZI"," userResponse":" MAJONZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333432593","data":{"timestamp":" 947333432593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333433408","data":{"timestamp":" 947333433408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333434243","data":{"timestamp":" 947333434243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333435019","data":{"timestamp":" 947333435019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333436234","data":{"timestamp":" 947333436234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGINE"," userResponse":" PENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333436849","data":{"timestamp":" 947333436849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333437904","data":{"timestamp":" 947333437904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUWA"," userResponse":" HALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333438529","data":{"timestamp":" 947333438529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333439094","data":{"timestamp":" 947333439094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333439799","data":{"timestamp":" 947333439799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333442143","data":{"timestamp":" 947333442142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333442805","data":{"timestamp":" 947333442804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333443415","data":{"timestamp":" 947333443415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333444790","data":{"timestamp":" 947333444790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333445965","data":{"timestamp":" 947333445965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333446720","data":{"timestamp":" 947333446720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333447365","data":{"timestamp":" 947333447365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333448469","data":{"timestamp":" 947333448469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINANE"," userResponse":" MINANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333449965","data":{"timestamp":" 947333449965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333451090","data":{"timestamp":" 947333451090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333453250","data":{"timestamp":" 947333453249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333454185","data":{"timestamp":" 947333454184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333454919","data":{"timestamp":" 947333454918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333456013","data":{"timestamp":" 947333456013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUPATA"," userResponse":" HAKUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333456777","data":{"timestamp":" 947333456777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333457581","data":{"timestamp":" 947333457581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333460361","data":{"timestamp":" 947333460361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333460424","data":{"timestamp":" 947333460423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333478129","data":{"timestamp":" 947333478129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" a5696f2d-a6a7-466b-89c2-6bd89b74118f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333498643","data":{"timestamp":" 947333498642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333502708","data":{"timestamp":" 947333502708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333506487","data":{"timestamp":" 947333506487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333512404","data":{"timestamp":" 947333512404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333516071","data":{"timestamp":" 947333516071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333520463","data":{"timestamp":" 947333520463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333527457","data":{"timestamp":" 947333527457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333531200","data":{"timestamp":" 947333531200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333535916","data":{"timestamp":" 947333535916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333540411","data":{"timestamp":" 947333540411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333544096","data":{"timestamp":" 947333544096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333548053","data":{"timestamp":" 947333548053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333553901","data":{"timestamp":" 947333553900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333557535","data":{"timestamp":" 947333557534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333561252","data":{"timestamp":" 947333561252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333565022","data":{"timestamp":" 947333565022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333568750","data":{"timestamp":" 947333568749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333572578","data":{"timestamp":" 947333572578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333576254","data":{"timestamp":" 947333576254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333580808","data":{"timestamp":" 947333580807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333584517","data":{"timestamp":" 947333584517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333588937","data":{"timestamp":" 947333588936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333592910","data":{"timestamp":" 947333592910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333596596","data":{"timestamp":" 947333596595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333599990","data":{"timestamp":" 947333599989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333605743","data":{"timestamp":" 947333605742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 8f7095aa-5bb9-4b60-9f76-7dde4bbbe37e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333623207","data":{"timestamp":" 947333623206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333629054","data":{"timestamp":" 947333629054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333632627","data":{"timestamp":" 947333632627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333636319","data":{"timestamp":" 947333636319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333639810","data":{"timestamp":" 947333639810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333645880","data":{"timestamp":" 947333645880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333649418","data":{"timestamp":" 947333649418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333653205","data":{"timestamp":" 947333653205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333656830","data":{"timestamp":" 947333656830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333662750","data":{"timestamp":" 947333662750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333668410","data":{"timestamp":" 947333668410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333672290","data":{"timestamp":" 947333672290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333678522","data":{"timestamp":" 947333678522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333682200","data":{"timestamp":" 947333682199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333685891","data":{"timestamp":" 947333685891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333689704","data":{"timestamp":" 947333689704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333693321","data":{"timestamp":" 947333693321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333699957","data":{"timestamp":" 947333699956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333703820","data":{"timestamp":" 947333703820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333708002","data":{"timestamp":" 947333708002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333714726","data":{"timestamp":" 947333714726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333718253","data":{"timestamp":" 947333718252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333722006","data":{"timestamp":" 947333722006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333725061","data":{"timestamp":" 947333725061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333731541","data":{"timestamp":" 947333731540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333736842","data":{"timestamp":" 947333736842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333740768","data":{"timestamp":" 947333740768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333744659","data":{"timestamp":" 947333744658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333748265","data":{"timestamp":" 947333748264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333752034","data":{"timestamp":" 947333752034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333757781","data":{"timestamp":" 947333757779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" ec26f400-aa01-47b1-a85f-96077c7dde7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333775299","data":{"timestamp":" 947333775299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333780488","data":{"timestamp":" 947333780488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333785488","data":{"timestamp":" 947333785487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333791321","data":{"timestamp":" 947333791321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333795272","data":{"timestamp":" 947333795271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333799044","data":{"timestamp":" 947333799043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333804732","data":{"timestamp":" 947333804732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333808264","data":{"timestamp":" 947333808264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333811840","data":{"timestamp":" 947333811840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333815407","data":{"timestamp":" 947333815407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333819426","data":{"timestamp":" 947333819426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333823120","data":{"timestamp":" 947333823120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333826977","data":{"timestamp":" 947333826977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333830169","data":{"timestamp":" 947333830168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333834136","data":{"timestamp":" 947333834135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333837412","data":{"timestamp":" 947333837412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333841132","data":{"timestamp":" 947333841132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333844563","data":{"timestamp":" 947333844562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333848360","data":{"timestamp":" 947333848360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333853913","data":{"timestamp":" 947333853912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333859352","data":{"timestamp":" 947333859352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333863032","data":{"timestamp":" 947333863032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333866402","data":{"timestamp":" 947333866402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333869680","data":{"timestamp":" 947333869680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333873340","data":{"timestamp":" 947333873340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333876985","data":{"timestamp":" 947333876984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333880517","data":{"timestamp":" 947333880517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333886918","data":{"timestamp":" 947333886918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333914778","data":{"timestamp":" 947333914777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333920574","data":{"timestamp":" 947333920571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 856a9366-6f45-4656-99bb-df24306ecdc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333938338","data":{"timestamp":" 947333938338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333944200","data":{"timestamp":" 947333944200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333951644","data":{"timestamp":" 947333951643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333959325","data":{"timestamp":" 947333959324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333963246","data":{"timestamp":" 947333963246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333968824","data":{"timestamp":" 947333968824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333974747","data":{"timestamp":" 947333974747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333981263","data":{"timestamp":" 947333981262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333984733","data":{"timestamp":" 947333984733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333988238","data":{"timestamp":" 947333988238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333993116","data":{"timestamp":" 947333993116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947333998334","data":{"timestamp":" 947333998334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334004524","data":{"timestamp":" 947334004524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334008472","data":{"timestamp":" 947334008472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334011996","data":{"timestamp":" 947334011995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334015286","data":{"timestamp":" 947334015286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334019158","data":{"timestamp":" 947334019157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334023381","data":{"timestamp":" 947334023380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334026909","data":{"timestamp":" 947334026909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334031155","data":{"timestamp":" 947334031155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334036672","data":{"timestamp":" 947334036672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334040304","data":{"timestamp":" 947334040304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334043911","data":{"timestamp":" 947334043911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334048006","data":{"timestamp":" 947334048005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334051697","data":{"timestamp":" 947334051697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334055287","data":{"timestamp":" 947334055287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334061093","data":{"timestamp":" 947334061093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334064947","data":{"timestamp":" 947334064947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334070875","data":{"timestamp":" 947334070875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334074542","data":{"timestamp":" 947334074541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334080308","data":{"timestamp":" 947334080307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 51e3bc30-13b4-4ef6-acf5-1876152090c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334100340","data":{"timestamp":" 947334100340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334104234","data":{"timestamp":" 947334104234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334108018","data":{"timestamp":" 947334108018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334111905","data":{"timestamp":" 947334111905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334118356","data":{"timestamp":" 947334118356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334122105","data":{"timestamp":" 947334122105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334126034","data":{"timestamp":" 947334126034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334132093","data":{"timestamp":" 947334132092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334135843","data":{"timestamp":" 947334135842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334140249","data":{"timestamp":" 947334140249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334144401","data":{"timestamp":" 947334144400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334148602","data":{"timestamp":" 947334148602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334152275","data":{"timestamp":" 947334152274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334155864","data":{"timestamp":" 947334155864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334159588","data":{"timestamp":" 947334159588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334163671","data":{"timestamp":" 947334163671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334167302","data":{"timestamp":" 947334167302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334171810","data":{"timestamp":" 947334171810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334178005","data":{"timestamp":" 947334178005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334181501","data":{"timestamp":" 947334181501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334184995","data":{"timestamp":" 947334184995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334188635","data":{"timestamp":" 947334188635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334192096","data":{"timestamp":" 947334192096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334195938","data":{"timestamp":" 947334195938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334199451","data":{"timestamp":" 947334199451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334204436","data":{"timestamp":" 947334204436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334208016","data":{"timestamp":" 947334208016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334213808","data":{"timestamp":" 947334213805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 1668f147-3827-40b9-8243-cfee3680c7e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334231641","data":{"timestamp":" 947334231641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334233701","data":{"timestamp":" 947334233701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334235787","data":{"timestamp":" 947334235787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334238918","data":{"timestamp":" 947334238918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334241172","data":{"timestamp":" 947334241171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334243429","data":{"timestamp":" 947334243428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334246298","data":{"timestamp":" 947334246298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334248440","data":{"timestamp":" 947334248440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334250585","data":{"timestamp":" 947334250585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334253731","data":{"timestamp":" 947334253731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334255779","data":{"timestamp":" 947334255778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334257819","data":{"timestamp":" 947334257819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334260750","data":{"timestamp":" 947334260749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334262958","data":{"timestamp":" 947334262957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334265206","data":{"timestamp":" 947334265205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334268287","data":{"timestamp":" 947334268286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334270641","data":{"timestamp":" 947334270641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334272969","data":{"timestamp":" 947334272968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334276065","data":{"timestamp":" 947334276064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334278235","data":{"timestamp":" 947334278234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334280407","data":{"timestamp":" 947334280406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334283573","data":{"timestamp":" 947334283572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334285766","data":{"timestamp":" 947334285765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334287950","data":{"timestamp":" 947334287949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334291135","data":{"timestamp":" 947334291134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334293563","data":{"timestamp":" 947334293563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334296034","data":{"timestamp":" 947334296033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334299192","data":{"timestamp":" 947334299191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334301447","data":{"timestamp":" 947334301446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334303691","data":{"timestamp":" 947334303690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334306704","data":{"timestamp":" 947334306703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334308941","data":{"timestamp":" 947334308941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334311172","data":{"timestamp":" 947334311171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334314139","data":{"timestamp":" 947334314138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334316505","data":{"timestamp":" 947334316504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334318878","data":{"timestamp":" 947334318878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334322020","data":{"timestamp":" 947334322019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334324446","data":{"timestamp":" 947334324446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334326836","data":{"timestamp":" 947334326835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334329814","data":{"timestamp":" 947334329813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334332102","data":{"timestamp":" 947334332102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334334407","data":{"timestamp":" 947334334406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334337651","data":{"timestamp":" 947334337650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334339900","data":{"timestamp":" 947334339899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334342199","data":{"timestamp":" 947334342199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334345581","data":{"timestamp":" 947334345581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334348015","data":{"timestamp":" 947334348014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334350447","data":{"timestamp":" 947334350446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334353333","data":{"timestamp":" 947334353332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334355537","data":{"timestamp":" 947334355536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334357770","data":{"timestamp":" 947334357769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334361199","data":{"timestamp":" 947334361199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334363567","data":{"timestamp":" 947334363566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334365889","data":{"timestamp":" 947334365889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334369035","data":{"timestamp":" 947334369034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334371288","data":{"timestamp":" 947334371288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334373590","data":{"timestamp":" 947334373590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334376644","data":{"timestamp":" 947334376644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334378798","data":{"timestamp":" 947334378797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334380939","data":{"timestamp":" 947334380938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334384105","data":{"timestamp":" 947334384104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334386393","data":{"timestamp":" 947334386392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334388669","data":{"timestamp":" 947334388669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334391873","data":{"timestamp":" 947334391872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334394104","data":{"timestamp":" 947334394103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334396336","data":{"timestamp":" 947334396336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334399616","data":{"timestamp":" 947334399616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334401987","data":{"timestamp":" 947334401986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334404325","data":{"timestamp":" 947334404324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334407502","data":{"timestamp":" 947334407501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334409844","data":{"timestamp":" 947334409844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334412212","data":{"timestamp":" 947334412211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334415636","data":{"timestamp":" 947334415634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334415750","data":{"timestamp":" 947334415750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334470520","data":{"timestamp":" 947334470520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_143722"," gameId":" 9280138b-13ac-472e-9832-1c52fd8fe2cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}